<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- generator="FeedCreator 1.7.2" -->
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Sakai Project News</title>
        <description>Sakai Project News Syndication</description>
        <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2006 17:00:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>FeedCreator 1.7.2</generator>
        <item>
            <title>Unicon and Sakai Present Latest Collaborative Learning Environment at EDUCAUSE Midwest Regional Conf</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=361&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>Source   Community Source Applications Gain Popularity with Higher Ed
Phoenix, AZ - March 10, 2006 - Unicon, Inc., the leading independent
provider of enterprise portal, collaboration, learning, and integration
technology for higher education institutions, will be sponsoring an
update of the Sakai...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Word from Walla Walla: Sakai and Smaller Institutions</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=357&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>&quot;Given the recent discussion involving Sakai, I thought I'd share Whitman College's experience with Sakai. 

Whitman is a small liberal arts college in rural Walla Walla, WA, with 1400 student FTE and an IT department with just 20 staff. Yet,...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NOW OPEN:  Sakai Conference Call for Proposals</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=356&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>Call for Proposals Now Open!  Submit your proposal. (https://sakaiproject.org/secure/vancouver/proposals/)   
As the Sakai community continues to grow, our bi-annual conferences
provide vital information and networking opportunities for developers,
instructional designers, implementers, faculty, and administrators. 
Start developing your proposals and plan...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Sakai 2.1.1 release is now available.</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=355&amp;Itemid=258</link>
            <description>The Sakai 2.1.1 release is now available.  The spirit behind the 2.1.1 release is to make fixes to the 2.1.0 code base that has been proven in a production environment available to the community. This release offers a total...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sakai Newsletter: February 9, 2006</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=353&amp;Itemid=533</link>
            <description>
Over 350 requirements now in Jira!

 Sakai 2.12 and OSP 2.1 Integration Week       
Call for Proposals for 5th Sakai Conference

New Lead for the Migration DG

Unicon Offers Faculty Low-Cost Service for Piloting Sakai
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>University of South Africas' myUnisa: 23750 course sites and growing</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=351&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>Unisa has Successfully Implemented Sakai 2.0.1:  myUnisa

After much hard work over December, Unisa successfully implemented
Sakai 2.0.1, called myUnisa, on 9 January 2006. We extend our sincere
thanks to the Sakai community who answered many questions and assisted
us with information. Below...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>OSP called &quot;one of the best-designed content management systems for education&quot;</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=350&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>In a recent NewsForge article, author Bruce Byfield offers a review of the Open Source Portfolio Iniative (http://www.osportfolio.org/%20target=blank) and calls it &quot;one of the best-designed content management system for education
that I have seen. Its attention to the user interface means...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sakai Vancouver '06 Conference Announcements</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=348&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>Community Source Week 2006 (http://www.sakaiproject.org/csw2006.html)
more details (index.php?option=com_content task=blogcategory id=170 Itemid=519)]

 
Hotel Reservations: Book your room today.  A block of hotel rooms has been reserved for the Sakai conference, so make your reservations early.  [ hotel info (index.php?option=com_content task=blogcategory...</description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
