<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<!-- generator="FeedCreator 1.7.2" -->
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Sakai Project News</title>
        <description>Sakai Project News Syndication</description>
        <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org</link>
        <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2006 11:17:33 +0100</lastBuildDate>
        <generator>FeedCreator 1.7.2</generator>
        <item>
            <title>Unicon Announces ''Sakai v2.1 Test Drive'' Open Source Learning Environment for Educators</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=318&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>Colleges and Universities Can Experience the Latest Sakai Tools -- Risk Free
 PHOENIX--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Dec. 15, 2005--Unicon, Inc., the leading
independent provider of enterprise portal, collaboration, learning, and
integration technology for higher education institutions, today
announced a new, hosted &quot;Sakai Test Drive&quot; program done...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Michigan, Indiana, MIT, Stanford Contribute Sakai Software to the Sakai Foundation, Sakai 2.1 ...</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=317&amp;Itemid=222</link>
            <description>PRESS RELEASE
Austin, Texas, USA --  6 December 2005  --
Michigan, Indiana, MIT, and Stanford Contribute Sakai Software to the
Sakai Foundation, Sakai 2.1 Released to the Public, 500+ Gather in
Austin for 7-9 December Conference 
     
mmiles@umich.edu...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>We Want Posters!</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=314&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>powerpoint template (/austin/sakai_poster_template.ppt) for you to use.  Create your poster using this template (http://www.sakaiproject.org/austin/sakai_poster_template.ppt), print it out and
bring it to the conference.  We'll hang these posters all over the
conference area throughout the conference.  
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sakai 2.1.0 released</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=313&amp;Itemid=258</link>
            <description>The Sakai 2.1.0 release is now available.  This release adds the
ability to manage sub-sections within course sites, and it has
redesigned several of the Sakai tools to take advantage of such
sections.  This sectioning facility represents the first stage of
employing...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Charles Sturt University commits to the Sakai Foundation</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=312&amp;Itemid=222</link>
            <description>Thursday 1st December 2005-- Charles Sturt University, Australia’s largest distance education
provider and a pioneer in online delivery today announced that it will
join some of the world’s leading universities in committing to the
support of the community source Sakai Foundation and in...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sakai Conference begins December 6th - Latest News and Updates</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=311&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>Updated --  List of Technical Demonstrations  (http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content task=blogcategory id=162 Itemid=499) planned for Thursday, December 8th

Have you already registered?  Then add your photo to the Sakai
Austin Facebook (https://sakaiproject.org/austin/facebook). 
Share your photo and interests and get to know other...</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>First Sakai Foundation Board Elections Results</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=304&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>The first Sakai Foundation Board elections have completed.  This
is another significant step in the development of the Sakai community
and its Foundation.  As many said, the field of nominees was so
strong that it was hard to choose among them....</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Sakai Foundation Board elections have begun, results are expected to be announced in early December</title>
            <link>http://www.sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content&amp;task=view&amp;id=303&amp;Itemid=312</link>
            <description>Three new Sakai board members will be elected by the
organizational representatives as specified in the Sakai Foundation
bylaws. A current list of  organizational representatives has been posted here (http://sakaiproject.org/index.php?option=com_content task=view id=104 Itemid=203#reps) .   The Sakai
community can view...</description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>
